use lmgvoiceapp



db.dummyjson.insert(
[
  {
    "Question": "What is the revenue from last two months?",
    "Keywords": "sales,revenue",
    "Answer": 120000,
    "Output": "the revenue from last two months is 120000"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which store received the maximum sales?",
    "Keywords": "maximum,highest",
    "Answer": "ABC",
    "Output": "ABC STORE RECEIVED THE MAXIMUM SALES"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which store received the minimum sales?",
    "Keywords": "minimum,lowest",
    "Answer": "QWE",
    "Output": "QWE STORE RECEIVED THE Minimum SALES"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which Apparel was sold most?",
    "Keywords": "Apparel",
    "Answer": "Shirt",
    "Output": "Shirt was sold most"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the average count of sold items in last six months?",
    "Keywords": "average count",
    "Answer": 2300,
    "Output": "An average of 2300 items were sold"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many non discounted item were sold?",
    "Keywords": "non-discounted",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Output": "30 non discounted items were sold"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many  discounted item were sold?",
    "Keywords": "discounted",
    "Answer": 524,
    "Output": "524 discounted items were sold"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which location is most popular for overall sales%uFFFD",
    "Keywords": "location",
    "Answer": "Yemlur",
    "Output": "the most popular location interms of overall sales is yemlur"
  },
  {
    "Question": "what is the most popular product sold?",
    "Keywords": "popular product",
    "Answer": "Jeans",
    "Output": "the most popular product sold is jeans"
  },
  {
    "Question": "source",
    "Keywords": "source",
    "Answer": "",
    "Output": "NoSql Mongo"
  }
]
)